Guide to the New York State Board of Mediation Cases 1952-1964
New York State Board of Mediation Cases
- A 60 - 700 to A 60 - 974 (1960). (Box 88)
  - A60-971 Hill's Supermarkets, Inc., 1960 (Box 88, Folder 100)
  - A60-972 Koster Bakeries, Inc., 1960 (Box 88, Folder 101)
  - A60-973 Duvernoy Bakeries, Inc., 1960 (Box 88, Folder 102)
  - A60-974 203 West 112th Street, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 103)
- Miscellaneous Arbitration Proceedings (1941-1945). (Box 89)
  - Arbitration Proceedings, 1944-1945 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Schenectady Railway Company and Schenectady Rapid Transit, 1942 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 475, 1943 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Herwitz Files, 1941-1944 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Local 32J, Building Service Employees International Union (A. F. L.), 1943 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Interpretation of Overtime Pay For Holidays, 1944 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Midtown Realty Owners Association, Inc., and Penn Zone Association, Inc., 1943 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Local 32B, 32J and 164, Building Service Employees International Union (A.F.L.) and Midtown Realty Owners Association, Inc., and Penn Zone Association, Inc., 1943 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Sperry Gyroscope Company, 1943 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Sperry Gyroscope Company, 1943 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - An Arbitration Childs Company vs Local 42 Volume 1, 1943 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Publishers Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity, 1944 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Mr. Paul R. Hays, 1943-1945 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Arbitration Proceedings (1944-1945). (Box 90)
  - Western Union Newspaper Clippings, 1944 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Western Union Newspaper Clippings, 1944 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity, 1944 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity and New York Daily Mirror, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity, 1944 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration between Third Avenue Transit Corporation, Surface Transportation Corp. of New York The Yonkers Railroad Company, Westchester St. Transportation Company, Inc., and The Westchester Electric Railroad Company, -and- Transport Workers Union of Ame, 1945 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Childs Company & Local 42; 1945 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - United Paper Workers Industrial Union, Local 292, C.I.O., -against- Brown, Lent & Pett, Employer, defending Party, 1941 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Proceedings Triboro Coach Corporation November 24, 1941 Volume 1 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration Proceedings Triboro Coach Corporation November 26th, 1941 Volume 2 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration Proceedings Triboro Coach Corporation November 26, 1941 Volume 3 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration Proceedings Triboro Coach Corporation November 27, 1941 Volume 4 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Proceedings Triboro Coach Corporation November 28, 1941 Volume 5 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Proceedings In the Matter of Manhattan Pontiac Corp. February 25, 1942 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Proceedings In the Matter of Manhattan Pontiac Corp. February 26, 1942 Volume (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Proceedings In the Matter of Manhattan Pontiac Corp. March 3rd, 1942 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration Proceedings In the Matter of Manhattan Pontiac Corp. March 9th, 1942 Volume 4 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Arbitration Proceedings (1942-1943). (Box 91)
  - Publishers' Association of New York City as Agent for some of it's Member Newspaper, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - The Arbitration Between Publishers' Association of New York City as Agent for Some of its Member Newspapers -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - The Arbitration between Publishers' Association of New York City, as Agent for some of its Member Newspapers -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - The Arbitration Between Publishers' Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of NYC and Vicinity., 1942 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Publishers' Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Publishers' Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Publishers' Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Publishers' Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Publishers' Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Publishers' Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Publishers' Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Publishers' Association of New York City -and- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - "Freezing of Jobs" vs. Reducing the Force, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Publishers of New York, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Arbitration Proceedings (1942-1943). (Box 92)
  - Pipe Line Exhibits, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Briefs and Opinion Application to Broadway Parties, 1942 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits for the Records (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Misc., 1928-1943 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Arbitration & Contracts, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Arbitration Proceedings (1943). (Box 93)
  - Bee Line Vol. 1 October 9, 1944 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Gottfried Baking Company minutes of Conference June 11, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Gottfried Baking Co. Inc. July 10, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Gottfried Baking Company, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Gottfried Baking Co. August 7, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Gottfried Baking co. Inc. July 31, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Charles Fischer Spring Company, 1944 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Selector - Roberts 1945 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration between Morton Coal Co. and Local 20571, A. F. of L., 1944 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration between Morton Coal Co. and Local 20571, 1944 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - In the Matter of Arbitration Bet. United Mutual Benefit Association & Industrial Insurance Agents Union Local 30, U.O.P.W.A., C.I.O., 1944 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Arbitration Awards (1946-1951). (Box 94)
  - Awards: Upstate - July to December 1951 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Awards: Upstate - January to June 1951 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Awards: New York City - December 1951 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Awards: New York City - October 1951 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Awards: New York City - September 1951 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Awards: New York City - August 1951 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Awards: New York City - July 1953, 1951-1953 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Awards: New York City - June 1951 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Awards: New York City - May 1951 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Awards: New York City - April 1951 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Awards: New York City - March 1951 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Awards: New York City - February 1951 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Awards: New York City - January 1951 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Awards: New York City - December 1950 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Awards: New York City - November 1950 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Awards: New York City - October 1950 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Awards: New York City - September 1950 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Awards: New York City - August 1950 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Awards: New York City - July 1950 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Awards: New York City - June 1950 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Awards: New York City - May 1950 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Awards New York City - April 1950 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Awards: New York City - March 1950 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Awards: Updates - July to December 1950 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Awards: Update - January to June 1950 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - 1949 Award: N.Y.C. (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Awards: Update - 1949 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Awards: Upstate - 1948 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Awards: Upstate- 1947 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - Awards: Upstate - 1946 (Box 94, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Arbitiration Awards (1952-1954). (Box 95)
  - Awards: New York City - December 1954 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - N.Y.C. Staff Awards November, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - N.Y.C. Staff Awards October,1954 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Awards: New York City - September 1954 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Awards: New York City - August 1954 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Awards: New York City - July 1954 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Awards: New York City - June 1954 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Awards: New York City - May 1954 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Awards: New York city - April 1954 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Awards: New York City - March 1954 Awards: New York City - March 1954 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Awards: New York City - February 1954 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Award: New York City - January 1954 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Awards: Buffalo 1954 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Awards: Albany -1954 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Awards: Syracuse - 1954 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Awards: New York City - December 1953 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Awards: New York City - November1953 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Awards: New York City - October 1953 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Awards: New York City - September 1953 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Awards: New York City - August 1953 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Awards: New York City - July 1953 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Awards: New York City - June 1953 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Awards: New York City - May 1953 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Awards: New York City - April 1953 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Awards: New York City - March 1953 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Awards: New York City - February 1953 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Awards: New York City - January 1953 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Awards: Albany - 1953 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Awards: Buffalo - 1953 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Awards: Syracuse - 1953 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Awards: Albany - 1953 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Awards: Buffalo - 1952 (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Awards: Syracuse - 1952 (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Awards: New York City - December 1952 (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - Awards: New York City - November 1952 (Box 95, Folder 35)
  - Awards: New York City - October 1952 (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - Awards: New York City - September 1952 (Box 95, Folder 37)
  - Awards: New York City - August 1952 (Box 95, Folder 38)
  - Awards: New York City - July 1952 (Box 95, Folder 39)
  - Awards: New York City June 1952 (Box 95, Folder 40)
  - Awards: New York City - May 1952 (Box 95, Folder 41)
  - Awards: New York City - April 1952 (Box 95, Folder 42)
  - Awards: New York City - March 1952 (Box 95, Folder 43)
  - Awards: New York City - February 1952 (Box 95, Folder 44)
  - Awards: New York City - January 1952 (Box 95, Folder 45)
- Taft-Hartley Disputes (1953-54). (Box 96)
  - New Jersey and Others, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - July 15 - July 31 - 1954 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - July 1- July 14- 1954 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - June 15 - June 90 1954 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - June 1 - June 14 - 1954 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - May 15 - May 31 1954 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - May 1 - May 14 - 1954 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - April 15 - April 30 - 1954 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - April 1 - April 14 - 1954 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - March 15, 1953 - March 30, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - February 28, 1953 - March 14, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - February 15, 1954 - February 27, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - January 31, 1954 - February 14, 1953, 1953-1954 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - January 15, 1954 - January 30, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - December 31, 1953 - January 13, 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Annual Reports (1917-1951). (Box 97)
  - 1937-1948 Annual Report Folder 1 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - 1937-1948 Annual Report Folder 2 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - 1917 - 1936 Annual Report (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - 1949 Annual Report (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - 1950 Annual Report (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - 1951 Annual Report, 1951-1952 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Annual Reports (1952-1956). (Box 97.1)
  - 1956 Annual Report of the New York State Board of Mediation (printed) (Box 97.1, Folder 1)
  - File Copies 1954-1955 Combined Annual Reports (Box 97.1, Folder 2)
  - Releases - 1954-1955 Annual Reports (Box 97.1, Folder 3)
  - Mailing Lists 1954-1955 Combined Annual Reports (Box 97.1, Folder 4)
  - 1954 Statistical Tables (were mimeographed) (Box 97.1, Folder 5)
  - 1954 Copies of Annual Report - Never Printed (Box 97.1, Folder 6)
  - 1954 Annual Report (Box 97.1, Folder 7)
  - 1952 Annual Report (Box 97.1, Folder 8)
  - 1953 Annual Report (Box 97.1, Folder 9)
  - 1950-1953 - Accomplishments of the New York State Board of Mediation (Box 97.1, Folder 10)
- Association of State Mediation Agencies - Proceedings; Correspondence. (Box 98)
  - ASMA "Intergroup Conflict and Its Mediation" by Arnold M. Rose and Caroline B. Rose, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings of Second Annual Meeting (Extra copies of Speeches), 1952 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - ASMA "Group Conflict and Its Mediation" by Arnold M. Rose, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - 1953 ASMA - Bulletins (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - 1953 - ASMA - Bulletins, extra copies, and stencils (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - 1953 Association of State Mediation Agencies (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Bulletin #6 - November 19, 1954 ASMA (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Bulletin #5 - September 27, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Feb. 19, 1954 - ASMA Bulletin #4 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - 1954 Association of State Mediation Agencies (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - ASMA - Minutes of Third Annual Meeting Madison, Wisconsin, 9/13-14/54, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Third Annual Meeting - Sept. 13, 14, 1954 ASMA (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - 1955 - Fourth Annual Conference ASMA (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - 1955 -ASMA Minutes of Fourth Annual Conference (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - 1955 Association of State Mediation Agencies (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - 1955 Association of State Mediation Agencies (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - 1954 Proceedings of Third Annual Conference ASMA (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - 1955 - ASMA Proceedings of Fourth Annual Conference (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - 1956 Association of State Mediation Agencies (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Association of State Mediation Agencies June 1953 - Second Annual Conference (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Association of State Mediation Agencies 1953 - Proceedings of Second Annual Meeting (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - 1952 Association of State Mediation Agencies (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - ASMA - Fifth Annual Conference - 1956 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - 1956 - Proceedings Fifth Annual Conference ASMA (Box 98, Folder 24)
- M1 - M193 (1938). (Box 99)
  - Long Island Lighting Co. Nassau & Suffolk Counties No. 174, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Collier Advertising Service, Inc. No. 162, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Busch Jewelry Stores No. 172, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Daily Eagle No. 42, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Cleaners & Dyers Board of Trade No. 132, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - United Shipbuilding Etc. No. 28, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Harlem Labor Union No. 79, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Woolworth Co., 1938 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - J.T. Sullivan Lumber Co. No. 124, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Green Mansions, Inc. No. 147, 1938-1939 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Gross, H. L. Co. M-173, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Window Cleaners Protective Union (Gotham Window Cleaning Co.) No. 89, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Bleyco Paper Corporation No. 132, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Heyman Glass Company Inc. No. 58, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Stanley & Patterson No. 49, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Geo. Stuhmer Baking Co. No. 46, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Lafayette Venetian Blind Co. Inc. No. 26, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Gimbel Bros. No. 23, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Micamold Condenser Corp. No. 20, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Furniture Frame Manufacturers' Assn.. No. 15, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - General Bronze Corp. No. 12, 1940 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - Bentley No. 10, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - M. & U. Meat Market No. 8, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - Littmanns, Inc. No. 1, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - Woodlawn Cemetery No. 116, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - Woodlawn Cemetery Fact Finding Board, 1936 (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - University Club No. 52, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - United Parcel Service No. 72, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 28)
  - Charles Weisbecker No. 76, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 29)
  - Ludwig Baumann No. 64, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - H.L. Green Company No. 65, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - John Mullins & Sons Furniture Company, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 32)
  - Greenway Cemetery Association No. 81, 1936-1940 (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - United Cigar-Whelan Stores Corporation No. 92, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 34)
  - San Remo Apartments No. 130, 1939 (Box 99, Folder 35)
  - Woolworth's No. 88, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 36)
  - Consolidated Edison Company No. 67, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 37)
  - Apeda Studio No. 66, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 38)
  - Drechsler Electric No. 68, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 39)
  - Gas Consumers Associations No. 189, 1937 (Box 99, Folder 40)
  - Atlantic Macaroni Company No. 185, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 41)
  - Commolite Corporation No. 123, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 42)
  - Associated Fur Coat & Trimming Mfrs., Inc. No. 113, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 43)
  - Photo Engravers Board of Trade of N. Y. Inc., 1938 (Box 99, Folder 44)
  - Garage Owners Associations No. 100, 1938-1939 (Box 99, Folder 45)
  - Horn & Hardart No. 95, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 46)
  - Greater New York Photo Finishers Assn. Inc. (Pavelle Laboratories, Inc.) No. 181, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 47)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company No. 96, 1938 (Box 99, Folder 48)
- M204 - M505 (1938/41). (Box 100)
  - Aerovox Corporation No. 204, 1938-1939 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - American Shoe Repairers Assn., Inc. No. 209, 1938 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Greater N.Y. Retail Furnishing & Dry Goods Metropolitan Merchants Assn. No. 212, 1938 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype Company, Inc. No. 228, 1939-1940 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - American Leather Specialties M-255, 1939-1940 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Brass Rail Et Al. M-256, 1941-1942 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Poetry Advisory Bd. On Labor Relations; Apartment House Owners M-257, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Association of Master Plumbers M-265, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Circle Wire & Cable Company and Four Others M-275, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Avenue B & East Bway Transit Co. M-283, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Greater New York Photo Finishers Assn. M-289, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Third Avenue Railroad company M-291, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Crystal Cab Corporation Embassy Transportation Corporation M-295, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Ludwig Baumann M-297, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - National Exhibition Company (Polo Grounds) M-299, 1939-1943 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Sperry Gyroscope Company Inc., 1939 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Starrett Lehigh Building M-307, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Bush Terminal Buildings Company M-312, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Montgomery Ward Co. M-315, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - St. Moritz Hotel on the Park M-316, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Liggett's Drug Stores M-317, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Texas Corporation, The M-333, 1939-1940 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Greater New York Retail Furnishings & Dry Goods Association M-336, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Retail Merchants Associated Board of Trade Inc. (H. Moser, Exec. Secretary) M-337, 1939-1940 (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Window Cleaners Employers Assn. M-340, 1939-1941 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Greenwood Cemetery Association M-354, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - Krum Confectionery & 677 (AFL) and 1115 (CIO) M-358, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Gleam Products M-365, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - Mergenthaler Linotype Company M-382, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - United Manufacturers Assn., Inc. (Greek Fur Mfrs.) M-383, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 30)
  - Nevins Inc. (Jos. Sartori) M-387, 1939 (Box 100, Folder 31)
  - Roger Smith Hotel White Plains, N.Y. M-390, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 32)
  - Steinway Omnibus Corporation Queensboro Bridge Railway Co., Inc. M-394, 1939-1940 (Box 100, Folder 33)
  - Masonic Temple M-395, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 34)
  - Euclid Candy Company M-397, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 35)
  - Lido Riviera M-408, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 36)
  - (Taxis) Paramelee System Terminal System, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 37)
  - Cold Storage Warehousemen's Assn. M-447, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 38)
  - Greater New York Lumber Dealers Assn. M-452, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 39)
  - Lane Bryant, Inc. M-454, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 40)
  - Cloak & Suit Industry M-455, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 41)
  - Bronx Terminal Markets Association M-456, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 42)
  - Metropolitan News Company M-457, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 43)
  - Lincoln Outfitting Company M-462, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 44)
  - Mullins Furniture Company, John M-468, 1941 (Box 100, Folder 45)
  - Broadcasting Systems & Radio Artists M-472, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 46)
  - Menters Credit Stores Inc. M-477, 1940 (Box 100, Folder 47)
  - Enrich, Henry & Co. M-499, 1941 (Box 100, Folder 48)
  - Plumbing & Hesting Wholesalers Assn. M-501, 1939-1942 (Box 100, Folder 49)
  - Briarcliff Laundry M-505, 1941 (Box 100, Folder 50)
- M506 - M770 (1941/42). (Box 101)
  - Cigarettes Merchandisers Assn. M-506, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - A. Krasne Wholesale Grocers M-514, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Baer Bros M-519, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Leviton Manufacturing Co. M-520, 1941-1942 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Cleaners & Dyers Board of Trade M-526, 1941-1942 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Publishing Co. M-528, 1941-1942 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Garage Board of Trade M-534, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Bates Chevrolet Corp. M-535, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Bee Line, Inc. M-539, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Jamaica Buses Inc. M-543, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Widder Bros., Inc. M-544, 1940-1942 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Woolworth Building M-550, 1940 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Ludwig Baumann Company M-553, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Empire City Supply Association M-562, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Ferries Operating Corp. M-563, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Consolidated Edison Co., Inc. M-567S (Supplementary), 1941 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Ford Instrument Co. Inc. M-579, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Childs Company M-582, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Publishers Association M-596, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Gold Star Venetian Blind Refinishing Company M-598, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - E. W. Bliss Company M-631, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Constance Hope Associates, Inc. M-637, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Midtown Reality Owners Assn. Inc. Penn Zone Assn. Inc. M-639, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Wholesale Grocers Assn. M-645, 1942-1943 (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Warshaw Mfg. Co., 1942-1943 (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - Motion Picture Companies (8) M-650, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 26)
  - Millinery Retailers Assn. of Greater New York, Inc., 1942 (Box 101, Folder 27)
  - R.C.A. Communications M-604, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 28)
  - Avenue B & East Broadway Transit Co., Inc. M-605, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 29)
  - Garment Suppliers Assn. M-606, 1941-1942 (Box 101, Folder 30)
  - Loft Candy Corp. M-660, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 31)
  - Manufacturers Machine & Tool Co., 1942 (Box 101, Folder 32)
  - Columbia Metal Frame Co. M-666, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 33)
  - Sigmund Cohn M-680, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 34)
  - French Bakers M-724, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 35)
  - Golden Baked et al. M-726, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 36)
  - Levy Bros. China Company, Inc. M0713, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 37)
  - Tidewater Association Oil Co. M-730, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 38)
  - United Parcel Service, Inc. M-735, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 39)
  - Ludwig Baumann & Company M-758, 1942 (Box 101, Folder 40)